(Amy(on webcam):)Well, normally I respect
your macho rebellious attitude
toward "The Man,"
(Amy(on webcam):)but, in this case, I think
you've made a foolish mistake.
(Sheldon:)Unlikely.
(Sheldon:)But make your case.
(Sheldon:)Keeping in mind that
your critical attitude
(Sheldon:)is ruining our
Saturday night together,
(Sheldon:)and I'm not above
minimizing your window.
(Amy:)Sheldon, like it or not,
(Amy:)until you manage
to upload your intelligence
(Amy:)into a self-sustaining
orbiting satellite,
(Amy:)equipped with high-speed
Internet and a cloaking device,
(Amy:)you will be dependent on other
members of the human race.
(Sheldon:)That's it.
Prepare to be minimized.
(Amy:)I'm not finished.
(Amy:)All scientists have
to fund-raise, Sheldon.
(Amy:)How do you think
I paid for my lab?
I went to Saudi Arabia
and met with a prince
who had an interest
in neurobiology.
(Sheldon:)Your lab is funded by some
Middle-Eastern dilettante?
(Amy:)Technically,
Faisal is my fiancé.
(Amy:)But I do have a state-of-the-art
two-photon microscope